Guide to the Time Inc. News Clippings 1999-2013 MS 3009-RG 20
New-York Historical Society
Time Inc. News Clippings
1999-2012
New-York Historical Society
Time, inc.
MS 3009-RG 20
54 Linear feet in 54 record cartons
The Time Inc. News Clippings contain copies of news articles about Time Warner and AOL Time Warner, its publications, and its subsidiaries.
Scope and Contents Note
The Time Inc. News Clippings contain copies of news articles about Time Warner and AOL Time Warner, its publications, and its subsidiaries collected by the Time Inc. Library and Archives. Corporate Communications compiled some of the clippings packets. Gaps in dates indicate clippings were not located, and it is unknown if folders of these clippings exist.
Arrangement Note
Organized chronologically.
Provenance
Gift of Time Inc. in 2015.
Related Archival Materials Note
This finding aid relates to just one record group of the Time Inc. Records. For information about the other record groups and for overall information about the archives, please see the Guide to the Time Inc. Records (MS 3009). The Henry Luce Papers (MS 3014) were acquired with the Time Inc. Records. The collection of books acquired with the records are cataloged as the Time Inc. Reference Library.
Access Restrictions
Open to qualified researchers. Materials are stored offsite and advance notice is required for use.
Accruals Note
Due to gaps in the dates, additional materials may exist and be added later.
Corporations -- History; Corporation records; Clippings (information artifacts).; Publishers and publishing -- New York (State) -- New York.; Organization files; Corporations -- New York (State) -- New York.; Time, inc. -- Archives; Time, inc. -- History
- News Clippings: 1999 January and August-December, 215396 (Offsite-box 1522)
- News Clippings: 2000 January-March, 215402 (Offsite-box 1523)
- News Clippings: 2000 April-July, 215403 (Offsite-box 1524)
- News Clippings: 2000 July-October, 215407 (Offsite-box 1525)
- News Clippings: 2000 October-2001 February, 2000-2001; 215409 (Offsite-box 1526)
- News Clippings: 2001 February-July, 215437 (Offsite-box 1527)
- News Clippings: 2001 August-2002 April, 2001-2002; 215438 (Offsite-box 1528)
- News Clippings: 2002 April-November, 215439 (Offsite-box 1529)
- News Clippings: 2002 November-2003 April, 2002-2003; 215440 (Offsite-box 1530)
- News Clippings: 2003 April-August, 215441 (Offsite-box 1531)
- News Clippings: 2003 August-October, 215442 (Offsite-box 1532)
- News Clippings: 2004 January (Offsite-box 2512)
- News Clippings: 2004 February-April (Offsite-box 2513)
- News Clippings: 2004 April-June (Offsite-box 2514)
- News Clippings: 2004 July-August, 231811 (Offsite-box 2511)
- News Clippings: 2004 September (Offsite-box 2514)
- News Clippings: 2004 October-December (Offsite-box 2515)
- News Clippings: 2004 December-2005 February, 2004-2005 (Offsite-box 2516)
- News Clippings: 2005 March-April (Offsite-box 2517)
- News Clippings: 2005 May-June, 231812 (Offsite-box 2195)
- News Clippings: 2005 July (Offsite-box 2512)
- News Clippings: 2005 August-September, 231813 (Offsite-box 2196)
- News Clippings: 2005 October-December, 215359 (Offsite-box 678)
- News Clippings: 2005 December-2006 February, 2005-2006; 215358 (Offsite-box 679)
- News Clippings: 2006 February-April, 215357 (Offsite-box 680)
- News Clippings: 2006 April-May, 215356 (Offsite-box 681)
- News Clippings: 2006 May-June, 215355 (Offsite-box 682)
- News Clippings: 2006 June-July, 215354 (Offsite-box 683)
- News Clippings: 2006 July-August, 215353 (Offsite-box 684)
- News Clippings: 2006 August-October, 215352 (Offsite-box 685)
- News Clippings: 2006 October-November, 215351 (Offsite-box 686)
- News Clippings: 2006 November-December, 215350 (Offsite-box 687)
- News Clippings: 2006 December-2007 January, 2006-2007; 215349 (Offsite-box 688)
- News Clippings: 2007 January-February, 215348 (Offsite-box 689)
- News Clippings: 2007 February-April, 215347 (Offsite-box 690)
- News Clippings: 2007 April-May, 215346 (Offsite-box 691)
- News Clippings: 2007 May-June, 215345 (Offsite-box 692)
- News Clippings: 2007 June-July, 215344 (Offsite-box 693)
- News Clippings: 2007 July-September, 215343 (Offsite-box 694)
- News Clippings: 2007 September-October, 215342 (Offsite-box 695)
- News Clippings: 2007 October-November, 215341 (Offsite-box 696)
- News Clippings: 2007 November-2008 January, 2007-2008; 215340 (Offsite-box 697)
- News Clippings: 2008 January-February, 215339 (Offsite-box 698)
- News Clippings: 2008 Febuary-April, 215338 (Offsite-box 699)
- News Clippings: 2008 April-July, 215337 (Offsite-box 700)
- News Clippings: 2008 July-October, 215336 (Offsite-box 701)
- News Clippings: 2008 October-2009 February, 2008-2009; 215335 (Offsite-box 702)
- News Clippings: 2009 February-July, 215334 (Offsite-box 703)
- News Clippings: 2009 July-December, 215333 (Offsite-box 704)
- News Clippings: 2009 December-2010 May, 2009-2010; 215332 (Offsite-box 705)
- News Clippings: 2010 May-August, 215331 (Offsite-box 706)
- News Clippings: 2010 August-2011 February, 2010-2011; 215330 (Offsite-box 707)
- News Clippings: 2011 February-July, 215329 (Offsite-box 708)
- News Clippings: 2011 July-October, 215328 (Offsite-box 709)
- News Clippings: 2011 October-2012 May, 2011-2012; 215327 (Offsite-box 710)
- News Clippings: 2012 June-2013 October, 2012-2013; 215326; 34 originally (Offsite-box 711)